http://www.bedzking.com/pages/terms-conditions

UPDATED 12/8/2020: Read a message about deliveries during the Holiday Season.
Warranty
Bunk Bed King Terms and Conditions.
Our goal at Bunk Bed King is to provide you with great products at low prices. To ensure you are comfortable with buying from us, the following Terms and Conditions apply when you visit our website and/or make a purchase from us. The Terms and Conditions are as follows:
Privacy PolicyYou can access full details of our privacy policy at Privacy Policy. Changes to our Privacy Policy, in whole or in part, will be indicated on our website.
Product InformationMaterial displayed on any of Bunk Bed King's websites is regularly checked for accuracy and is presented "AS IS", without any warranties, expressed or implied. Information on any of the Bunk Bed King websites might contain typographical errors, inaccuracies and/or omissions. These are unintentional.
Should a product be listed at an incorrect price or the description of the product displays erroneous information as the result of typographical errors or errors in pricing or other incorrect information from our manufacturers, we reserve the right to refuse or cancel any of these orders listed at an incorrect price, even if your credit card has already been charged.
In the event that the order was confirmed and your credit card charged, we will immediately issue a credit in the exact amount of the charge to your credit card. We apologize for the inconvenience this might cause you. Bunk Bed King makes every effort to accurately display colors of products appearing on our websites. However, because the colors you see directly depend on your monitor settings, Bunk Bed King cannot guarantee that your monitor will accurately display the colors of items on our websites.
OrderingYou can access full details of our ordering procedures at Ordering.
PaymentsYou can access full details of our payment options at Payments.
ShippingYou can access full details of how we ship your orders at Shipping.
ReturnsYou can access full details on our return policies see Returns.
Links to Third Party SitesThe Bunk Bed King website may include links to websites owned, operated and maintained by third parties. We have no control over these websites. When you access these linked websites, please be aware that the privacy policies on these third-party websites may be different from our own. Before submitting any personal information on any other website, read the privacy policy of the linked website first.
Disclaimer and Limitation of LiabilityThis website is provided by Bunk Bed King on an "AS IS" basis. Information on this website might contain typographical errors, inaccuracies and/or omissions. These are unintentional, therefore, Bunk Bed King shall not be held responsible for said typographical errors, inaccuracies and/or omissions. Further, Bunk Bed King reserves the right to correct errors, inaccuracies and omissions, and change and/or update information without prior notice, including errors, inaccuracies and/or omissions related to product descriptions, pricing, and availability. Bunk Bed King makes no representations or warranties of any kind, express or implied, as to the operation of the website or the information, content, materials, or products included on the website. Use of any products purchased from this website must be in accordance with the safety warnings and general notes provided with the product. To the fullest extent permitted by applicable law, Bunk Bed King expressly disclaims all warranties, conditions and/or representations, expressed or implied, as to the use of the website and the products sold on our websites. This disclaimer includes, but is not limited to, the implied warranties of merchantability and fitness for a particular purpose. Further, Bunk Bed King does not warrant (and explicitly disclaims any warranty) that the website (and any of our affiliated websites) or the server(s) that makes it available are free of viruses or other harmful components, it being the user's responsibility to determine whether any information downloaded from our websites is free of viruses, worms, trojan horses, or other items of a potentially harmful nature. Any link between Bunk Bed King and any other website does not constitute an endorsement of the linked or affiliated website. Bunk Bed King does not make any warranty as to the content of other websites linked to Bunk Bed King.
Under no circumstances shall Bunk Bed King or any of its managers, agents, employees, affiliates, subsidiaries, or any other representatives be liable to you or anyone else for any direct, indirect, incidental, special, punitive, consequential, exemplary, or other damages incurred by you or any third party, whether in an action in contract or in tort, arising from accessing, using or the inability to use, this website or any related matters regarding products sold on our websites.
Applicable LawYou agree to comply with all applicable laws, statutes, ordinances and regulations regarding your use of any of our websites, and your purchase of products and/or services through any of our websites. Any infraction of these Terms and Conditions shall be governed by the laws of the state of Texas without regard to any conflict of law provisions of your domicile residence or physical location. At our discretion, we may report any infractions or violations relating to these Terms and Conditions to the appropriate authorities. You and Bunk Bed King each agree to submit to the personal and exclusive jurisdiction of the appropriate state and federal courts located within Tarrant County, Texas in respect of any disputes.
The failure of Bunk Bed King to exercise or enforce any right or provision set forth in these Terms and Conditions shall not constitute a waiver of such right or provision. If any provision of these Terms and Conditions is found by a court of competent jurisdiction to be invalid, the parties nevertheless agree that the court should endeavor to give effect to the parties' intentions as reflected in the provision, and the other provisions of these Terms and Conditions shall remain in full force and effect. You agree that regardless of any statute or law to the contrary, any claim or cause of action sounding in contract arising out of or related to the use of the website (including, but not limited to, any purchase of products or services through the site) must be filed within two (2) years and one (1) day after such claim or cause of action arose or be forever barred. You further agree that regardless of any statute or law to the contrary, any claim or cause of action sounding in tort arising out of or related to the use of the site (including, but not limited to, any purchase of products or services through the site) must be filed within one (1) year after such claim or cause of action arose or be forever barred. If you do not agree to be bound by the above Terms and Conditions, you should immediately discontinue your use of this site. Use of this site constitutes acceptance of these Terms and Conditions.
Copyright and Trademark NoticeAll screens appearing on our websites including graphics, text, design, buttons, logos, images, and icons, as well as the selection, assembly, and arrangement, are the sole property of Bunk Bed King or its suppliers and/or licensors, and are protected by U.S. and international copyright laws. The content on our websites is only for the purpose of shopping on the websites or placing an order and for no other purpose. Any other use, including modification, reproduction, uploading, posting, transmission, or distribution in any form or by any means without Bunk Bed King's prior written permission, is strictly prohibited. All software used on the websites is the sole property of Bunk Bed King or those supplying the software.
Bunk Bed King is a registered trademark. In addition, graphics, logos, page headers, button icons, scripts, and service names included in or made available through our websites are trademarks or trade dress of Bunk Bed King in the U.S. and other countries or are the property of their respective owners. All rights not expressly granted herein are reserved.
Bunk Bed King - Quality at Discount Prices with Free Shipping
